<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <author>
    <name>SeedRamp</name>
  </author>
  <id>seedramp.com</id>
  <title>SeedRamp</title>
  <updated>2016-03-12T01:10:16.881148+00:00</updated>
  <entry>
    <author>
      <name>Yegor Bugayenko</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/02/20/LegalRobot.html</id>
    <link href="http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/02/20/LegalRobot.html"/>
    <published>2016-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <summary>&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intro&lt;/strong&gt;.
        This was our 10th interview and I was very skeptical. To be honest,
        I even forgot about it, but Dan emailed me just a few hours before the
        appointment. It was a Saturday morning at 10am. I told Dan that previous
        interviews were not successful and he had to be ready for a negative answer.
        He said no problem, at least some feedback would be helpful. With that far from optimistic
        mood, we started.&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;div style=&quot;width:50%;float:right;z-index:100;margin-left:1em;&quot;&gt;
          &lt;div class=&quot;film&quot;&gt;
            &lt;iframe class=&quot;video&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AetgrIGCrSU?controls=2&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;/&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product&lt;/strong&gt;.
        &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.legalrobot.com&quot;&gt;LegalRobot&lt;/a&gt; is a hosted software solution for parsing legal documents
        and finding abnormalities within them. That's how I understood it, at least. You can
        upload a PDF contract and in a few seconds get a summary of what
        looks suspicious. For example, clause 8.3 is too much against the buyer.
        The software contains a machine learning engine that basically compares
        a huge amount of similar documents with the one you uploaded. The smarter
        the engine, the more accurate the answers.&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market&lt;/strong&gt;.
        The product is already on the market, if Dan was telling the truth. There
        are a few beta-users already uploading some documents there and trying to
        use the system. Moreover, there are over 300 subscribers who expressed
        their interest in the system. I doubt that even 10% of them will become
        real clients, but it's very important to see that Dan is focused on
        bringing his product to users.&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competition&lt;/strong&gt;.
        There are a few companies that are technically doing the exact same thing. However,
        according to Dan, they are all focused on lawyers. Their target users
        are attorneys, while &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.legalrobot.com&quot;&gt;LegalRobot&lt;/a&gt;
        is for those who want to do those verifications
        without paying legal fees. I truly believe that taking lawyers out of the
        market as much as possible, and replacing them with computer systems, is
        definitely the right strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team&lt;/strong&gt;.
        &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/danrubins&quot;&gt;Dan&lt;/a&gt;
        is a CEO, an architect and a programmer. I was glad to see that.
        In general, I believe in startups managed and founded by technical people,
        who are real authors of their products. There are a few freelancers helping
        him. That's exactly the type of startup team I'm comfortable investing in.&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash&lt;/strong&gt;.
        Dan put his own money into this and someone else also added $25,000 a few
        months ago. His burn rate is around $3,000 per month, which sounds very
        reasonable. He basically spends most of this money paying his own bills.
        That's a perfect tactic for a young startup, I believe. He is
        planning to raise seed or series A money in a few months and needs
        cash to survive until then. He asked for $20,000 but I offered him $5,000
        for the next calendar month. If things go well, the product
        will be ready for a demo (it wasn't during the interview) and beta-users will produce
        some traction. He may come back to us again and we'll invest another portion
        of cash to cover the next calendar month.&lt;/p&gt;
        
        &lt;p&gt;On Monday, Dan emailed me the contract, we signed it electronically, and I've
        sent him a wire transfer for $5,000. We're partners!&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
          Yegor Bugayenko
          &lt;br&gt;
          SeedRamp LLC
          &lt;br&gt;
          2016-02-20
        &lt;/br&gt;
      &lt;/br&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;</summary>
    <title>First $5,000 for LegalRobot</title>
    <updated>2016-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2016-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <dc:date>2016-03-12T01:10:16.881148+00:00</dc:date>
</feed>
