"target/log/2016/07/29/Privme.html"
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<html>
  <head>
    <meta charset="utf-8"/>
    <meta content="width=device-width,minimum-scale=1,initial-scale=1" name="viewport"/>
    <meta content="seed fund, venture capital, startup, seed investment" name="keywords"/>
    <meta content="Third investment transaction goes to a well done B2C marketing tool." name="description"/>
    <meta content="2016-07-29T00:00:00+00:00" name="published"/>
    <link href="/images/logo-64x64.png?8d8c192" rel="shortcut icon"/>
    <title>$10,000 for Privme</title>
    <link href="http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/07/29/Privme.amp.html" rel="amphtml"/>
    <link type="text/css" href="/css/plain.css?8d8c192" rel="stylesheet"/>
    <meta content="Yegor Bugayenko" name="author"/>
  </head>
  <body>
    <article>
      <div class="logo">
        <a href="/">
          <img alt="logo" class="noprint" height="100px" src="/images/logo.svg?REVISION" width="100px"/>
        </a>
      </div>
      <h1>$10,000 for Privme</h1>
      <div id="content">
        <p><strong>Update!</strong>: Lakshmi complained about this article and sent me this: "We soft launched in Feb 2016 and we signed up 8 national test merchants (eg. Five Guys, Yogurtland, Quiznos), 150+ Bay Area merchants and have 100,000+ deals in the platform." Thus, I believe they are doing better than I understood from the interview :)</p>
        <p><strong>Intro</strong>. As a user, I like the idea of <a href="http://www.privme.com">Privme</a>, a lot. Listen up, you download an app, connect it with your Facebook, Instagram and whatever it is. Then, you let it screen your bank account (just like QuickBooks does, for example) and you're all set. Now Privme knows a lot about your buying habits. It knows where you're eating, how often you check in, how much you're spending, etc. Then, a restaurant across the street downloads another Privme app and literally says: "I will give 25% to everybody who is eating in this town frequently and is an active Facebook user". The restaurant doesn't want to just give 25% to everybody (like Groupon does), but only to those who are potential active and loyal customers. Impressive, huh? I believe, it's the next step after Groupon.</p>
        <div style="width:50%;float:right;z-index:100;margin-left:1em">
          <div class="film">
            <iframe class="video" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DIfperQ5c2k?controls=2">&#x200B;</iframe>
          </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Product</strong>. <a href="http://www.privme.com">Privme</a> consists of three pieces, as far as I understood it: a server side, a mobile app for a buyer and a mobile app for a merchant. They all were created by <a href="https://angel.co/lakshmi-m-kodali">Lakshmi</a>, <a href="https://angel.co/pavan-kumar-rao-cheeti">Pavan</a>, and there small team of developers oversees (I forgot where exactly). Rather complex piece of software and they claimed they invested over $400k+ and over 16 months in building it.</p>
        <p><strong>Market</strong>. The product is on the market. Lakshmi said that seven restaurants are already on board plus one enterprise (to optimize dining for their employees). What I didn't like is that they've spent so much time on development of the product without testing it on the market first. That's a very typical mistake and it may be critical in their case. Hope they will manage to survive under the pressure of initial market reaction.</p>
        <p><strong>Competition</strong>. There are many similar solutions, for example Groupon. But they are not doing exactly the same. They don't actually solve the problem of merchants  giving discounts to potentially loyal customers and ignoring the rest. All that Groupon-like solutions are doing more harm to businesses than benefits. However, I'm afraid that something exactly the same as Privme is already somewhere in development or on the market. If that's the case, I hope that Lakshmi will be faster than others.</p>
        <p><strong>Team</strong>. I only spoke to Lakshmi and he sounded like a down-to-earth practical guy, which is the type I personally like. He's also a programmer himself, with an experience in making products for marketing industry.</p>
        <p><strong>Cash</strong>. They said that they invested $400k+ up to date. I'm not sure whether the number was exactly that, but definitely a lot of effort was spent to make it. The software product is rather big and works well. However, they haven't had any investments up to date and that's a negative side. We're literally their first seed investor. I can only hope that Lakshmi will focus on raising more seed money immediately. Without money this business idea will be in a big danger. I also promised Lakshmi to introduce him to a number of investors I know.</p>
        <p>So, we signed SAFE and I've mailed them a check for $10K. We're partners!</p>
        <p>Yegor Bugayenko<br/>SeedRamp LLC<br/>2016-07-29 00:00:00 +0000</p>
      </div>
    </article>
    <script type="text/javascript">!function(e,a,t,n,c,o,s){e.GoogleAnalyticsObject=c,e[c]=e[c]||function(){(e[c].q=e[c].q||[]).push(arguments)},e[c].l=1*new Date,o=a.createElement(t),s=a.getElementsByTagName(t)[0],o.async=1,o.src=n,s.parentNode.insertBefore(o,s)}(window,document,"script","//www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js","ga"),ga("create","UA-1963507-40","auto"),ga("send","pageview")</script>
  </body>
</html>
"target/log/2016/04/12/JobNow.html"
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<html>
  <head>
    <meta charset="utf-8"/>
    <meta content="width=device-width,minimum-scale=1,initial-scale=1" name="viewport"/>
    <meta content="seed fund, venture capital, startup, seed investment" name="keywords"/>
    <meta content="This is our second investment, a rather risky but promising one" name="description"/>
    <meta content="2016-04-12T00:00:00+00:00" name="published"/>
    <link href="/images/logo-64x64.png?8d8c192" rel="shortcut icon"/>
    <title>$5,000 for JobNow</title>
    <link href="http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/04/12/JobNow.amp.html" rel="amphtml"/>
    <link type="text/css" href="/css/plain.css?8d8c192" rel="stylesheet"/>
    <meta content="Yegor Bugayenko" name="author"/>
  </head>
  <body>
    <article>
      <div class="logo">
        <a href="/">
          <img alt="logo" class="noprint" height="100px" src="/images/logo.svg?REVISION" width="100px"/>
        </a>
      </div>
      <h1>$5,000 for JobNow</h1>
      <div id="content">
        <p><strong>Intro</strong>. This was one of the first online interviews for us. I was not yet sure whether we can invest at all, without seeing and "touching" the candidate. But after all everything went well and easy. You can watch it.</p>
        <div style="width:50%;float:right;z-index:100;margin-left:1em">
          <div class="film">
            <iframe class="video" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/F-ljB4TPiRE?controls=2">&#x200B;</iframe>
          </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Product</strong>. <a href="http://www.jobnow.me">JobNow</a> is a job interview scheduling platform. When you need a contractor for a few hours (a waiter, a chef, or a cashier), just submit that position to the system and wait. Very soon, some candidates will apply and immediately schedule interviews. You won't need to select them, email them, or call them. They will just who up in your calendar and next day in your office. It's literally a job right now solution.</p>
        <p><strong>Market</strong>. They already have paying customers, according to Roberto. And that customers seem to be happy. I don't think this is entirely true, since the platform needs to have enough candidates to make paying customers happy. However, I was glad to see that Roberto has put the product on the market already and is not afraid of earning first dollars even with the system that is not yet fully implemented.</p>
        <p><strong>Competition</strong>. There are many platforms for job search, but there is nothing like JobNow. Well, according to my knowledge and Roberto's words. That makes this startups even more interesting.</p>
        <p><strong>Team</strong>. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/robertoinetti">Roberto</a> is a CEO, an architect and a programmer. That's the configuration I like most of all. Besides that, he's got a pretty successfull career <a href="https://500px.com/robertoinetti">as a photographer</a>. This basically means that he can achieve something.</p>
        <p><strong>Cash and Investors</strong>. Roberto put his own money into this product. I was going to become the first investor. This is basically was the only negative thing in this deal. Roberto was obviously not fully prepared for raising more money. But he had to be! I strongly adviced him to focus on that in the next few months. We'll see how he will manage that.</p>
        <p>Right after the interview I prepared SAFE for Roberto, emailed it to him and got his electronic signature. Then, sent him a $5,000 wire transfer. We're partners!</p>
        <p>Yegor Bugayenko<br/>SeedRamp LLC<br/>2016-04-12 00:00:00 +0000</p>
      </div>
    </article>
    <script type="text/javascript">!function(e,a,t,n,c,o,s){e.GoogleAnalyticsObject=c,e[c]=e[c]||function(){(e[c].q=e[c].q||[]).push(arguments)},e[c].l=1*new Date,o=a.createElement(t),s=a.getElementsByTagName(t)[0],o.async=1,o.src=n,s.parentNode.insertBefore(o,s)}(window,document,"script","//www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js","ga"),ga("create","UA-1963507-40","auto"),ga("send","pageview")</script>
  </body>
</html>
"target/log/2016/02/20/LegalRobot.html"
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<html>
  <head>
    <meta charset="utf-8"/>
    <meta content="width=device-width,minimum-scale=1,initial-scale=1" name="viewport"/>
    <meta content="seed fund, venture capital, startup, seed investment" name="keywords"/>
    <meta content="We made our first investment decision and we think it was a good one." name="description"/>
    <meta content="2016-02-20T00:00:00+00:00" name="published"/>
    <link href="/images/logo-64x64.png?8d8c192" rel="shortcut icon"/>
    <title>First $5,000 for LegalRobot</title>
    <link href="http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/02/20/LegalRobot.amp.html" rel="amphtml"/>
    <link type="text/css" href="/css/plain.css?8d8c192" rel="stylesheet"/>
    <meta content="Yegor Bugayenko" name="author"/>
  </head>
  <body>
    <article>
      <div class="logo">
        <a href="/">
          <img alt="logo" class="noprint" height="100px" src="/images/logo.svg?REVISION" width="100px"/>
        </a>
      </div>
      <h1>First $5,000 for LegalRobot</h1>
      <div id="content">
        <p><strong>Intro</strong>. This was our 10th interview and I was very skeptical. To be honest, I even forgot about it, but Dan emailed me just a few hours before the appointment. It was a Saturday morning at 10am. I told Dan that previous interviews were not successful and he had to be ready for a negative answer. He said no problem, at least some feedback would be helpful. With that far from optimistic mood, we started.</p>
        <div style="width:50%;float:right;z-index:100;margin-left:1em">
          <div class="film">
            <iframe class="video" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AetgrIGCrSU?controls=2">&#x200B;</iframe>
          </div>
        </div>
        <p><strong>Product</strong>. <a href="http://www.legalrobot.com">LegalRobot</a> is a hosted software solution for parsing legal documents and finding abnormalities within them. That's how I understood it, at least. You can upload a PDF contract and in a few seconds get a summary of what looks suspicious. For example, clause 8.3 is too much against the buyer. The software contains a machine learning engine that basically compares a huge amount of similar documents with the one you uploaded. The smarter the engine, the more accurate the answers.</p>
        <p><strong>Market</strong>. The product is already on the market, if Dan was telling the truth. There are a few beta-users already uploading some documents there and trying to use the system. Moreover, there are over 300 subscribers who expressed their interest in the system. I doubt that even 10% of them will become real clients, but it's very important to see that Dan is focused on bringing his product to users.</p>
        <p><strong>Competition</strong>. There are a few companies that are technically doing the exact same thing. However, according to Dan, they are all focused on lawyers. Their target users are attorneys, while <a href="http://www.legalrobot.com">LegalRobot</a> is for those who want to do those verifications without paying legal fees. I truly believe that taking lawyers out of the market as much as possible, and replacing them with computer systems, is definitely the right strategy.</p>
        <p><strong>Team</strong>. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/danrubins">Dan</a> is a CEO, an architect and a programmer. I was glad to see that. In general, I believe in startups managed and founded by technical people, who are real authors of their products. There are a few freelancers helping him. That's exactly the type of startup team I'm comfortable investing in.</p>
        <p><strong>Cash</strong>. Dan put his own money into this and someone else also added $25,000 a few months ago. His burn rate is around $3,000 per month, which sounds very reasonable. He basically spends most of this money paying his own bills. That's a perfect tactic for a young startup, I believe. He is planning to raise seed or series A money in a few months and needs cash to survive until then. He asked for $20,000 but I offered him $5,000 for the next calendar month. If things go well, the product will be ready for a demo (it wasn't during the interview) and beta-users will produce some traction. He may come back to us again and we'll invest another portion of cash to cover the next calendar month.</p>
        <p>On Monday, Dan emailed me the contract, we signed it electronically, and I've sent him a wire transfer for $5,000. We're partners!</p>
        <p>Yegor Bugayenko<br/>SeedRamp LLC<br/>2016-02-20 00:00:00 +0000</p>
      </div>
    </article>
    <script type="text/javascript">!function(e,a,t,n,c,o,s){e.GoogleAnalyticsObject=c,e[c]=e[c]||function(){(e[c].q=e[c].q||[]).push(arguments)},e[c].l=1*new Date,o=a.createElement(t),s=a.getElementsByTagName(t)[0],o.async=1,o.src=n,s.parentNode.insertBefore(o,s)}(window,document,"script","//www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js","ga"),ga("create","UA-1963507-40","auto"),ga("send","pageview")</script>
  </body>
</html>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <author>
    <name>SeedRamp</name>
  </author>
  <id>seedramp.com</id>
  <title>SeedRamp</title>
  <updated>2017-05-08T10:06:54.492709+00:00</updated>
  <entry>
    <author>
      <name>Yegor Bugayenko</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/07/29/Privme.html</id>
    <link href="http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/07/29/Privme.html"/>
    <published>2016-07-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <summary>&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update!&lt;/strong&gt;: Lakshmi complained about this article and sent me this: &quot;We soft launched in Feb 2016 and we signed up 8 national test merchants (eg. Five Guys, Yogurtland, Quiznos), 150+ Bay Area merchants and have 100,000+ deals in the platform.&quot; Thus, I believe they are doing better than I understood from the interview :)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intro&lt;/strong&gt;. As a user, I like the idea of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.privme.com&quot;&gt;Privme&lt;/a&gt;, a lot. Listen up, you download an app, connect it with your Facebook, Instagram and whatever it is. Then, you let it screen your bank account (just like QuickBooks does, for example) and you're all set. Now Privme knows a lot about your buying habits. It knows where you're eating, how often you check in, how much you're spending, etc. Then, a restaurant across the street downloads another Privme app and literally says: &quot;I will give 25% to everybody who is eating in this town frequently and is an active Facebook user&quot;. The restaurant doesn't want to just give 25% to everybody (like Groupon does), but only to those who are potential active and loyal customers. Impressive, huh? I believe, it's the next step after Groupon.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div style=&quot;width:50%;float:right;z-index:100;margin-left:1em&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;film&quot;&gt;
      &lt;iframe class=&quot;video&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DIfperQ5c2k?controls=2&quot;&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.privme.com&quot;&gt;Privme&lt;/a&gt; consists of three pieces, as far as I understood it: a server side, a mobile app for a buyer and a mobile app for a merchant. They all were created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://angel.co/lakshmi-m-kodali&quot;&gt;Lakshmi&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://angel.co/pavan-kumar-rao-cheeti&quot;&gt;Pavan&lt;/a&gt;, and there small team of developers oversees (I forgot where exactly). Rather complex piece of software and they claimed they invested over $400k+ and over 16 months in building it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market&lt;/strong&gt;. The product is on the market. Lakshmi said that seven restaurants are already on board plus one enterprise (to optimize dining for their employees). What I didn't like is that they've spent so much time on development of the product without testing it on the market first. That's a very typical mistake and it may be critical in their case. Hope they will manage to survive under the pressure of initial market reaction.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competition&lt;/strong&gt;. There are many similar solutions, for example Groupon. But they are not doing exactly the same. They don't actually solve the problem of merchants  giving discounts to potentially loyal customers and ignoring the rest. All that Groupon-like solutions are doing more harm to businesses than benefits. However, I'm afraid that something exactly the same as Privme is already somewhere in development or on the market. If that's the case, I hope that Lakshmi will be faster than others.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team&lt;/strong&gt;. I only spoke to Lakshmi and he sounded like a down-to-earth practical guy, which is the type I personally like. He's also a programmer himself, with an experience in making products for marketing industry.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash&lt;/strong&gt;. They said that they invested $400k+ up to date. I'm not sure whether the number was exactly that, but definitely a lot of effort was spent to make it. The software product is rather big and works well. However, they haven't had any investments up to date and that's a negative side. We're literally their first seed investor. I can only hope that Lakshmi will focus on raising more seed money immediately. Without money this business idea will be in a big danger. I also promised Lakshmi to introduce him to a number of investors I know.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;So, we signed SAFE and I've mailed them a check for $10K. We're partners!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yegor Bugayenko&lt;br/&gt;SeedRamp LLC&lt;br/&gt;2016-07-29 00:00:00 +0000&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</summary>
    <title>$10,000 for Privme</title>
    <updated>2016-07-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2016-07-29T00:00:00+00:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <author>
      <name>Yegor Bugayenko</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/04/12/JobNow.html</id>
    <link href="http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/04/12/JobNow.html"/>
    <published>2016-04-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <summary>&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intro&lt;/strong&gt;. This was one of the first online interviews for us. I was not yet sure whether we can invest at all, without seeing and &quot;touching&quot; the candidate. But after all everything went well and easy. You can watch it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div style=&quot;width:50%;float:right;z-index:100;margin-left:1em&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;film&quot;&gt;
      &lt;iframe class=&quot;video&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/F-ljB4TPiRE?controls=2&quot;&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jobnow.me&quot;&gt;JobNow&lt;/a&gt; is a job interview scheduling platform. When you need a contractor for a few hours (a waiter, a chef, or a cashier), just submit that position to the system and wait. Very soon, some candidates will apply and immediately schedule interviews. You won't need to select them, email them, or call them. They will just who up in your calendar and next day in your office. It's literally a job right now solution.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market&lt;/strong&gt;. They already have paying customers, according to Roberto. And that customers seem to be happy. I don't think this is entirely true, since the platform needs to have enough candidates to make paying customers happy. However, I was glad to see that Roberto has put the product on the market already and is not afraid of earning first dollars even with the system that is not yet fully implemented.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competition&lt;/strong&gt;. There are many platforms for job search, but there is nothing like JobNow. Well, according to my knowledge and Roberto's words. That makes this startups even more interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/robertoinetti&quot;&gt;Roberto&lt;/a&gt; is a CEO, an architect and a programmer. That's the configuration I like most of all. Besides that, he's got a pretty successfull career &lt;a href=&quot;https://500px.com/robertoinetti&quot;&gt;as a photographer&lt;/a&gt;. This basically means that he can achieve something.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash and Investors&lt;/strong&gt;. Roberto put his own money into this product. I was going to become the first investor. This is basically was the only negative thing in this deal. Roberto was obviously not fully prepared for raising more money. But he had to be! I strongly adviced him to focus on that in the next few months. We'll see how he will manage that.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Right after the interview I prepared SAFE for Roberto, emailed it to him and got his electronic signature. Then, sent him a $5,000 wire transfer. We're partners!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yegor Bugayenko&lt;br/&gt;SeedRamp LLC&lt;br/&gt;2016-04-12 00:00:00 +0000&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</summary>
    <title>$5,000 for JobNow</title>
    <updated>2016-04-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2016-04-12T00:00:00+00:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <author>
      <name>Yegor Bugayenko</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/02/20/LegalRobot.html</id>
    <link href="http://www.seedramp.com/log/2016/02/20/LegalRobot.html"/>
    <published>2016-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <summary>&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intro&lt;/strong&gt;. This was our 10th interview and I was very skeptical. To be honest, I even forgot about it, but Dan emailed me just a few hours before the appointment. It was a Saturday morning at 10am. I told Dan that previous interviews were not successful and he had to be ready for a negative answer. He said no problem, at least some feedback would be helpful. With that far from optimistic mood, we started.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div style=&quot;width:50%;float:right;z-index:100;margin-left:1em&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;film&quot;&gt;
      &lt;iframe class=&quot;video&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AetgrIGCrSU?controls=2&quot;&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.legalrobot.com&quot;&gt;LegalRobot&lt;/a&gt; is a hosted software solution for parsing legal documents and finding abnormalities within them. That's how I understood it, at least. You can upload a PDF contract and in a few seconds get a summary of what looks suspicious. For example, clause 8.3 is too much against the buyer. The software contains a machine learning engine that basically compares a huge amount of similar documents with the one you uploaded. The smarter the engine, the more accurate the answers.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market&lt;/strong&gt;. The product is already on the market, if Dan was telling the truth. There are a few beta-users already uploading some documents there and trying to use the system. Moreover, there are over 300 subscribers who expressed their interest in the system. I doubt that even 10% of them will become real clients, but it's very important to see that Dan is focused on bringing his product to users.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competition&lt;/strong&gt;. There are a few companies that are technically doing the exact same thing. However, according to Dan, they are all focused on lawyers. Their target users are attorneys, while &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.legalrobot.com&quot;&gt;LegalRobot&lt;/a&gt; is for those who want to do those verifications without paying legal fees. I truly believe that taking lawyers out of the market as much as possible, and replacing them with computer systems, is definitely the right strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/danrubins&quot;&gt;Dan&lt;/a&gt; is a CEO, an architect and a programmer. I was glad to see that. In general, I believe in startups managed and founded by technical people, who are real authors of their products. There are a few freelancers helping him. That's exactly the type of startup team I'm comfortable investing in.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cash&lt;/strong&gt;. Dan put his own money into this and someone else also added $25,000 a few months ago. His burn rate is around $3,000 per month, which sounds very reasonable. He basically spends most of this money paying his own bills. That's a perfect tactic for a young startup, I believe. He is planning to raise seed or series A money in a few months and needs cash to survive until then. He asked for $20,000 but I offered him $5,000 for the next calendar month. If things go well, the product will be ready for a demo (it wasn't during the interview) and beta-users will produce some traction. He may come back to us again and we'll invest another portion of cash to cover the next calendar month.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;On Monday, Dan emailed me the contract, we signed it electronically, and I've sent him a wire transfer for $5,000. We're partners!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yegor Bugayenko&lt;br/&gt;SeedRamp LLC&lt;br/&gt;2016-02-20 00:00:00 +0000&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</summary>
    <title>First $5,000 for LegalRobot</title>
    <updated>2016-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <dc:date>2016-02-20T00:00:00+00:00</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <dc:date>2017-05-08T10:06:54.492709+00:00</dc:date>
</feed>
